Guide to the Wunderman Archives, 1946-2010 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Awards, 1986-2010 and undated, (20 boxes)
  - Large-Format Materials
    - Caples Awards
      - 1991, American Express Establishment Services/KLM Europe By Design Offer (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Apple (Box AW9)
      - 1991, AT&T (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Autofleet (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Bayer, Baypen (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Dupont (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Gevalia Kaffe Import Service (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Jaguar (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Mercedes-Benz (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Music Club (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Notebook computer (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Operation Welcome Home (Box AW9)
      - 1991, SIP (Professional Information Services) (Spain) (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Small cigars (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Swedish DM Day (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Trade finance (Box AW9)
      - 1991, TV Guide Magazine (Box AW9)
      - 1991, USPS (Box AW9)
      - 1995, Air France (Box AW9)
      - 1995, American Express (Box AW9)
      - 1995, Apple (Box AW9)
      - 1995, AT&T (Box AW9)
      - 1995, Dupont (Box AW9)
      - 1995, Entry form and official rules (Box AW9)
      - 1995, Sears (Box AW9)
    - Echo Awards
      - 1990, American Express (Box AW9)
      - 1990, Andersen Consulting (Box AW9)
      - 1990, Apple (Box AW9)
      - 1990, AT&T (Box AW9)
      - 1990, Columbia House (Box AW9)
      - 1990, Time-Life Books (Box AW9)
      - 1990, Time Warner, Inc. (Box AW9)
      - 1991, Adidas Styles Ltd. (Box AW9)
      - 1991, ALA Services S.P.A. (Box AW9)
      - 1991, American Express (Box AW9)
    - 1991, Apple (Box AW10)
      - 1991, AT&T (Box AW10)
      - 1991, AVL- Time/System (Austria) (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Book-of-the-Month Club (Box AW10)
      - 1991, City of New York (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Colgate Palmolive (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Columbia House (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Columbia House Canada (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Dannemann Cigarrenfabrik (Germany) (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Dupont (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Ford Motor Company (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Hill's Pet Products (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Kraft General/Foods International (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Mitsui Home Co., Ltd. (Japan) (Box AW10)
      - 1991, Nippon Suisan Kaisha, Ltd. (Box AW10)
    - 1991, The Norwegian Telecom (Box AW11)
      - 1991, Robert Bosch Italia S.P.A. (Box AW11)
      - 1991, Sony Nederland B.V. (Holland) (Box AW11)
      - 1991, Time Warner, Inc. (Box AW11)
      - 1991, United States Postal Service (Box AW11)
      - 1991, Wunderman Worldwide (New York) (Box AW11)
      - 1991, Wunderman Worldwide Limited (Box AW11)
      - 1991, Wunderman Marketing Directo (Box AW11)
      - 1991, Zenith (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Air Afrique (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Air France (Box AW11)
      - 1992, American Express (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Apple (Box AW11)
      - 1992, British Airways (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Caja Espana (Spain) (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Columbia House (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Dupont Do Brasil (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Entry form (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Japan Tupperware Co., Ltd. (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Les Echos (French Newspaper- April 7, 1992) (Box AW11)
      - 1992, PTT Nederland (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Stockholm Energi (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Time Warner, Inc. (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Venturini (Milan) (Box AW11)
      - 1992, Zung Fu Company, Ltd. (Box AW11)
      - 1999, Echo Awards DM News- October 25, 1999 (Box AW11)
    - New York Festivals
      - 1994, International Print & Radio Advertising Awards (Box AW11)
    - Lester Wunderman Awards
      - 2010, Entries
        - Amsterdam/Antwerp (Box AW12)
          - Ford, Hugo Boss, Microsoft (Box AW12)
        - Bangkok
          - Smirnoff (Box AW12)
        - Beijing
          - Nokia (Box AW12)
        - Boston
          - AT&T (Box AW12)
        - Buenos Aires
          - Coca-Cola, Ford, Microsoft (Box AW12)
        - Chicago
          - DiGiorno, Sears, Xbox (Box AW12)
        - Cologne
          - Ford (Box AW12)
        - Detroit
          - Ford (Box AW12)
        - Frankfurt (Box AW13)
          - Dell, Land Rover, Lufthansa (Box AW13)
        - Hamburg
          - Airtours, Luxury Pirates (Box AW13)
        - Hong Kong
          - Festive Hong Kong, Microsoft, MSN, Prudential (Box AW13)
        - Irvine
          - Invisalign, Southern California Edison (SCE) (Box AW13)
        - London (Box AW14)
          - Best Buy, Ford, Kern Precision Scales, Land Rover, Microsoft, Nokia, Procter & Gamble Pringles (Box AW14)
        - Melbourne (Box AW15)
          - Ford, Kraft, Wunderman (Box AW15)
        - Mexico City
          - Ford, Tri de Corazón (Box AW15)
        - Milan
          - Microsoft (Box AW15)
        - Munich
          - Microsoft (Box AW15)
        - New York
          - Black Rock, Dell, Huggies, Land Rover/Range Rover, Nokia (Box AW15)
        - Paris (Box AW16)
          - Microsoft (Box AW16)
        - Prague
          - Tipsport (Box AW16)
        - Sao Paulo
          - Ford, Johnny Walker, Land Rover, Microsoft, Perdigão, Smirnoff, Vivo (Box AW16)
        - Seattle (Box AW17)
          - Alaska Airlines, Entertainment Weekly, Expedia, Microsoft, Xbox (Box AW17)
        - Shanghai
          - Yue Sai (L'Oreal) (Box AW17)
        - Shenfield
          - Mazda (Box AW17)
        - Singapore
          - Xbox (Box AW17)
        - Sydney (Box AW18)
          - Australian government My School, Microsoft, Nokia, World Wildlife Federation (Box AW18)
        - Toronto
          - Microsoft (Box AW18)
        - Vancouver
          - Ball Talk, Starbucks (Box AW18)
        - Vienna
          - Austrian Airlines, dm Drogeriemarkt, Ford, Land Rover, Microsoft, Wunderman (Box AW18)
        - Zurich (Box AW19)
          - David gegen Goliath, Ford, Phonak, Reporters Without Borders, Sonova, Terres des Hommes (Box AW19)
        - Dubai (Box AW20)
          - Planet Mars (Box AW20)
        - Jakarta
          - Mizone Flashmob, Nokia (Box AW20)
        - Madrid
          - BBVA, Ford, Iberia Airlines, Land Rover, Microsoft, Movistar (Box AW20)
        - Seattle
          - Alllure Bays Corp. (Box AW20)
        - Singapore
          - Nokia (Box AW20)
        - Taipei
          - Singleton (Box AW20)
- International Offices, 1980-2000 and undated, (80 boxes)
  Includes documentation relation to the operation and creative output of Wunderman's international partners and subsidiary offices. Additional materials relating to international operations may be found in the Account Files Series. Arranged alphabetically by country and office location.
  - Argentina (Buenos Aires)
    - American Express, 1992-1993 (Box IO1)
    - Aquarium Mar del Plata, 1994, 1996, (2 folders) (Box IO1)
    - Argentina Direct Marketing Association, 1997 (Box IO1)
    - AT&T, 1997 (Box IO1)
    - Colgate, 1994 (Box IO1)
    - Converse, 1995 (Box IO1)
    - Cuisine & Vins, 1997 (Box IO1)
    - Disco supermarkets, 1995-1996 (Box IO1)
    - DuPont, 1993-1994 (Box IO1)
    - Ford (Box IO1)
    - Creative, 1997 (Box IO1)
    - Ka, 1997 (Box IO1)
    - Member Get-a-Member program, 1997 (Box IO1)
    - Friskies, 1997 (Box IO1)
    - Goupe Danone (Villa del Sur), 1997, (2 folders) (Box IO1)
    - IBM, 1997 (Box IO1)
    - La Buenos Aires, 1993 (Box IO1)
    - Metropolitan Life/American Express, 1996 (Box IO1)
    - Program (Lufenuron), 1996 (Box IO1)
    - Skytel, 1995 (Box IO1)
    - Telecom/Paginas Amarillas, 1995 (Box IO1)
    - Xerox, 1996 (Box IO1)
  - Australia (Adelaide)
    - Adelaide Central Mission/Lifeline, 1994 (Box IO2)
    - Adelaide Convention and Tourist Authority, 1993-1995 (Box IO2)
    - Allowrie Foods (Golden North), 1992-1993 (Box IO2)
    - Bank of South Australia, 1994 (Box IO2)
    - Clipsal, 1993 (Box IO2)
    - Farmers' Union Iced Coffee, 1995 (Box IO2)
    - Faulding Pharmaceuticals (Algistat), undated (Box IO2)
    - Grahams Jewelers, undated (Box IO2)
    - MFP (Multi-Function Polis) Australia, undated (Box IO2)
    - Mitsubishi, 1994-1996, (2 folders) (Box IO2)
    - Orlando Wyndham (Havana Club rum), 1995 (Box IO2)
    - Rundle Mall, undated (Box IO2)
    - South Australia Ambulance Service, 1995 (Box IO2)
  - Australia (Melbourne)
    - Australia Post, 1990 (Box IO3)
    - Citibank Visa creative, 1998 (Box IO3)
    - Dulux Paint, 1996 (Box IO3)
    - DuPont Tyvek, 1995-1996 (Box IO3)
    - Esanda Finance (Box IO3)
    - Creative and case study, 1990-1996 and undated, (2 folders) (Box IO3)
    - Women in Business, undated (Box IO3)
    - Florigene, 1997 (Box IO3)
    - Land's End, 1995-1996 (Box IO3)
    - Minolta, undated (Box IO3)
    - National Dairies, Ltd., 1995 (Box IO3)
    - Powercor creative, 1997-1999 (Box IO3)
    - South Cape Outfitters, 1997 (Box IO3)
    - Tabcorp, 1997 (Box IO3)
  - Australia (Sydney)
    - American Express, 1996-1997 (Box IO4)
    - American Express Small Business Alliance, 1997 (Box IO4)
    - Amway of Australia, 1994 (Box IO4)
    - Apple, 1990-1997, (3 folders) (Box IO4)
    - Australian Direct Marketing Association, 1995 (Box IO4)
    - Code Blue/Horizon brand cigarettes (WD & HO Wills Ltd.), 1995-1996 (Box IO4)
    - Colgate (Box IO4)
    - General, 1994 (Box IO4)
    - Reports, 1993-1994 (Box IO4)
    - Reports on grocery and retail trade, 1994 (Box IO4)
    - Foxtel (Box IO4)
    - General, 1995-1997, (2 folders) (Box IO4)
    - 31 Incredible Channels Upgrade, 1996 (Box IO5)
    - Braveheart, 1996 (Box IO5)
    - Children's acquisition, circa 1996 (Box IO5)
    - Magazine, 1996 (Box IO5)
    - Marketing overview with samples, 1996 (Box IO5)
    - Phenomenal mailing, 1996 (Box IO5)
    - UKTV, undated (Box IO5)
    - Free Phone Australia Ltd., undated (Box IO5)
    - Frito-Lay/Space Jam board game, 1996 (Box IO5)
    - Novell, undated (Box IO5)
    - NRMA Life Insurance, 1990-1991 (Box IO5)
    - Optus Communications, 1993-1995, (3 folders) (Box IO5)
    - Sydney Harbour Casino, 1995-1997 (Box IO5)
    - Worldwide Management Meeting materials, 1991 (Box IO5)
    - Xerox, 1996 (Box IO5)
    - Yogo snack foods, undated (Box IO5)
  - Austria (Vienna)
    - British Airways, 1996 (Box IO6)
    - Bundesliga football league, 1996 (Box IO6)
    - Ericsson, 1997 (Box IO6)
    - Europapier, 1994-1996 (Box IO6)
    - Ford (Box IO6)
    - Customer loyalty program, 1996-1997 (Box IO6)
    - Galaxy launch, 1995 (Box IO6)
    - Mailers, 1990-1992 (Box IO6)
    - Mobil, 1994 (Box IO6)
    - Nike, 1996 (Box IO6)
    - Swissair, 1996 (Box IO6)
    - Victorinox, 1995 (Box IO6)
    - WWF Austria, 1995 (Box IO6)
  - Belgium (Brussels)
    - Canal+, 1991 (Box IO6)
    - Chefard Belgium (Predictor pregnancy test), undated (Box IO6)
    - Citibank Visa creative, 1990 (Box IO6)
    - Dion Eggs, 1994-1995 (Box IO6)
    - Eternit, 1996 (Box IO6)
    - Inza, 1993-1995 (Box IO6)
    - Lufthansa, 1996 (Box IO6)
    - Siemans Telecommunications, 1994-1995 (Box IO6)
    - Tele Kwinto Cable lottery game, 1994 (Box IO6)
    - WCJ self-promotion/new business, 1994 (Box IO6)
  - Brazil (Rio de Janeiro)
    - Abril Coleções (video collection) case study, undated (Box IO7)
    - AT&T Global Calling Card, undated (Box IO7)
    - ATL Communications creative, 1999 (Box IO7)
    - Cimiento Mauá (cement), 1997 (Box IO7)
    - Clinica Perintal Laranjerias mailer, 1999 (Box IO7)
    - Digital Computers creative, 1999 (Box IO7)
    - Estação do Corpo spa mailers, 1999 (Box IO7)
    - TVA creative, 1998 (Box IO7)
    - Varig Airlines creative, 1999 (Box IO7)
  - Brazil (São Paulo)
    - American Express (Box IO7)
    - Robin Hood project, 1993 (Box IO7)
    - Travel/life insurance, 1996 and undated (Box IO7)
    - American Home, 1997 (Box IO7)
    - Cheque Apetik Alimentação, 1991 (Box IO7)
    - Chivas Regal, undated (Box IO7)
    - Citibank creative, 1998 and undated, (2 folders) (Box IO7)
    - Club Med, undated (Box IO7)
    - Colgate, 1994-1996, (2 folders) (Box IO7)
    - Colgate oral hygiene research, 1996, (2 folders) (Box IO7)
    - Cultura Artistica, 1990-1993 (Box IO8)
    - Direct marketing special projects, 1995 (Box IO8)
    - DuPont case study, undated (Box IO8)
    - Ericsson, undated (Box IO8)
    - Ford (Box IO8)
    - Courier, undated (Box IO8)
    - Creative, 1998-1999 (Box IO8)
    - Escort, 1997 (Box IO8)
    - Fiesta, 1997 (Box IO8)
    - Ka launch, circa 1996 (Box IO8)
    - Test drive program, 1997 (Box IO8)
    - Y&R Brazil print advertisements (Box IO8)
    - IBM creative and case study, 1998 and undated (Box IO8)
    - Jack Daniels, 1991-1993 (Box IO8)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken, undated (Box IO8)
    - Mesbla, 1996 (Box IO8)
    - National Bank/Unibanco (Banquinho Turma da Mônica) children's savings account program, 1995 (Box IO8)
    - Oglobo, 1993-1994 (Box IO8)
    - Prever, 1994 (Box IO8)
    - TVA, undated (Box IO8)
    - TVA Cable, 1994 (Box IO8)
    - Various clients, 1991 and undated (Box IO8)
  - Canada (Toronto)
    - Air France USA, 1991-1996 (Box IO9)
    - Air Miles (Box IO9)
    - Brand equity building project, 1997 (Box IO9)
    - Mailers, 1995-1997 (Box IO9)
    - American Express, document for meeting with Wunderman, 1991 (Box IO9)
    - Apple, 1991-1997, (3 folders) (Box IO9)
    - ARCO (gas stations)/AMPM (convenience stores), work by Firstcom, 1996 (Box IO9)
    - AT&T, 1994-1997, (2 folders) (Box IO9)
    - Budget Rental Cars (Firstcom), 1995 (Box IO9)
    - Burger King (Firstcom), 1994-1997 (Box IO9)
    - Canadian Direct Marketing Association, 1995-1997 (Box IO10)
    - Canadian Tire Retail Card, 1995-1996 (Box IO10)
    - Colgate (Firstcom)--Includes cookbook, Quick & Easy Casseroles, 1988-1994 (Box IO10)
    - Colgate Oral Care Report, 1991-1997 (Box IO10)
    - Columbia House (Firstcom), 1992-1995 (Box IO10)
    - Co-Operative Housing Federation of Canada/HB Group insurance brochure, undated (Box IO10)
    - Co-operators Insurance (Directprotect), 1996-1997 (Box IO10)
    - Deckers Grill buttons, 1997 and undated (Box IO10)
    - Digital Hinote Ultra notebook computer (Firstcom), 1995 (Box IO10)
    - DuPont (Box IO10)
    - Case studies (Firstcom), 1994 (Box IO10)
    - Creative (Firstcom), 1994 (Box IO10)
    - Tyvek, 1993-1994 (Box IO10)
    - Financial Post (Box IO11)
    - Case study, 1995 (Box IO11)
    - Coffee promotion, 1995 (Box IO11)
    - Ford (Box IO11)
    - Case studies (Firstcom), 1992-1995 (Box IO11)
    - Creative (Firstcom)--English and Spanish, 1988-1998 (Box IO11)
    - Escort (Firstcom), 1996 (Box IO11)
    - Irving Oil (Firstcom), 1997 (Box IO11)
    - Kodak (Firstcom), 1993 (Box IO11)
    - Labatt Breweries, 1993 (Box IO11)
    - Merrell Dow Pharmaceuticals (Seldane), 1993 (Box IO11)
    - Midas (Firstcom), 1994 (Box IO11)
    - Minolta (Firstcom), 1995 (Box IO11)
    - Public Service Alliance of Canada (Coughlin & Associates), 1996 (Box IO11)
    - Royal Bank Credit Line, 1996-1997 (Box IO11)
    - Tetra Pak creative, 1998 (Box IO11)
    - Undercurrents promotion, undated (Box IO11)
    - United States Postal Service, Valuepost Canada, undated (Box IO11)
    - WWF Canada, 1992-1993 (Box IO11)
    - Xerox, 1994-1995 (Box IO11)
    - Yves Rocher, 1995-1996 (Box IO11)
  - Chile (Santiago)
    - Agro Gas, 1995-1996 (Box IO12)
    - Citibank (Box IO12)
    - Morpheus pillow, undated (Box IO12)
    - Spinning Top, undated (Box IO12)
    - Visa (Y&R Direct), undated (Box IO12)
    - Federal Express, 1993 (Box IO12)
    - Ford, 1997 (Box IO12)
    - Home Center, 1995 (Box IO12)
    - LAN Chile (ChileAir), 1995 (Box IO12)
    - Lipigas, 1994-1995 (Box IO12)
    - L'Oreal, 1996 (Box IO12)
    - Pepsi, 1996 (Box IO12)
    - Transbank, 1995, (2 folders) (Box IO12)
    - WCJ Chile self-promotion, 1995 (Box IO12)
    - Xerox, 1995 (Box IO12)
  - China (Hong Kong)
    - Apple Club launch, 1996 (Box IO12)
    - Bosch Power Tools, undated (Box IO12)
    - DuPont Lycra, 1994-1995 (Box IO12)
    - Federal Express, 1992-1995 (Box IO12)
    - Franklin Mint, 1997 (Box IO12)
    - Hong Kong Sports Development Board, 1993 (Box IO12)
    - Johnny Walker Premier, 1995 (Box IO12)
    - Mercedes Benz SEC launch, 1994 (Box IO12)
    - Mitsui Home mailers, undated (Box IO12)
    - Shell loyalty program, 1995 (Box IO12)
    - Star TV (English and Arabic), 1997 (Box IO12)
  - Colombia (Bogota)
    - BIMA furniture, 1995 (Box IO13)
    - Citibank (Box IO13)
    - Case study, 1996 (Box IO13)
    - Creative, 1998 (Box IO13)
    - Miscellaneous creative, 1995 (Box IO13)
    - Philips Batteries, 1995 (Box IO13)
    - Texaco (with medallion), 1997 (Box IO13)
    - WCJ self-promotion, 1997 (Box IO13)
    - Xerox case study, undated (Box IO13)
  - Czech Republic (Prague)
    - Amora condiments, undated (Box IO13)
    - Bond Street cigarettes (Philip Morris), 1994-1997 (Box IO13)
    - Danone (Box IO13)
    - General, 1995 (Box IO13)
    - Lucky five, 1995 (Box IO13)
    - Space Jam tie-in, undated (Box IO13)
    - Ford, 1996-1997 (Box IO13)
    - Milka, 1996 (Box IO13)
    - Volvo interactive, 1999 (Box IO13)
  - Denmark (Copenhagen)
    - Colgate, 1989-1990 (Box IO13)
    - Danish Post (Box IO13)
    - Creative, 1987-1992, (2 folders) (Box IO13)
    - Report, 1992 (Box IO13)
    - Denmark Olympic Committee, 1993 (Box IO14)
    - Ford (Box IO14)
    - Creative, 1994 (Box IO14)
    - Ka creative, 1997-1998 (Box IO14)
    - Girobank, 1995-1996 (Box IO14)
    - Kraft Jacobs Suchard (Imperial Coffee Club), 1995 (Box IO14)
    - KTAS (Copenhagen Telephone), circa 1984 (Box IO14)
    - Nestlé-Disney tie-in, 1994 (Box IO14)
    - Nycomed Dak (Letigen), 1996 (Box IO14)
    - Scandinavisk Industries, 1996 (Box IO14)
    - Shell Oil, 1993 (Box IO14)
    - Sony, 1994 (Box IO14)
    - Sprite (Coca-Cola), 1989 (Box IO14)
    - Statoil, 1995-1996 (Box IO14)
    - WCJ self-promotion, alcohol tester, undated (Box IO14)
  - Dominican Republic (Santo Domingo)
    - Colgate, 1994 (Box IO14)
    - Nestlé (Y&R Damaris), 1993 (Box IO14)
  - Finland (Helsinki)
    - Apple, 1993 (Box IO14)
    - Nobi, 1995 (Box IO14)
    - OY Organon AB (Gracial contraceptive pill), undated (Box IO14)
    - Phohjola Insurance, 1988 (Box IO14)
    - Rabo-Radiobiooking, circa 1987 (Box IO14)
    - Scan, 1995-1996 (Box IO14)
    - WCJ self-promotion, 1996 (Box IO14)
  - France (Lyon)
    - Auchan Porte de Alpes (WXYR Groupe Young & Rubicam), 1990 (Box IO15)
  - France (Paris)
    - Air Afrique, 1991-1993 (Box IO15)
    - Air France, 1994 (Box IO15)
    - Alcatel, 1992-1994 (Box IO15)
    - American Express (Box IO15)
    - General, 1996 (Box IO15)
    - Reports, 1991-1994 (Box IO15)
    - SAS tie-in, 1995 (Box IO15)
    - Andersen Consulting, undated (Box IO15)
    - ANEIC (Covema cider), undated (Box IO15)
    - Bailey's Irish Cream, 1991 (Box IO15)
    - Bandai (Nintendo), 1992 (Box IO15)
    - BCMW shelf space optimization, undated (Box IO15)
    - Bonduelle, 1996-1997 (Box IO15)
    - British Airways Executive Club, 1995 (Box IO15)
    - Canal+, 1990-1997 (Box IO15)
    - Cogesal (Marco Bellini), 1990-1991 (Box IO15)
    - Colgate, 1989-1990 (Box IO15)
    - Compaq, 1990 (Box IO15)
    - Danone (Box IO15)
    - General, 1992-1997 (Box IO15)
    - Bingo, 1993-1996, (2 folders) (Box IO15)
    - Case studies (international), 1993-1997 (Box IO15)
    - Case studies, 1994 (Box IO16)
    - Collect'O, 1997 (Box IO16)
    - Creative, 1999 (Box IO16)
    - Reports, 1993-1997 (Box IO16)
    - DHL International Express Courier, 1995 (Box IO16)
    - Dole (Covema), 1994 (Box IO16)
    - EDF (Electricté de France), 1989-1992 (Box IO16)
    - Ericsson, 1997 (Box IO16)
    - Eurotunnel Le Shuttle, 1995-1997 (Box IO16)
    - Ford (Box IO16)
    - Cougar mailers, 1999 (Box IO16)
    - Puma, 1997 (Box IO16)
    - Hiram Walker (Ballantine's Whiskey), 1993 (Box IO16)
    - IDV/Sovedi (Box IO16)
    - Malibu, 1991 (Box IO16)
    - Smirnoff Blue, 1990 (Box IO16)
    - Infomatin, 1994 (Box IO16)
    - Jacadi children's clothes, 1992 (Box IO16)
    - Jacques Vabre/KJS (El Gringo coffee), 1992 (Box IO16)
    - Kraft (Box IO16)
    - Airship tour, 1993 (Box IO16)
    - Hollywood chewing gum, 1991-1996 (Box IO16)
    - Kraft Jacobs Suchard (Milka chocolate bar), 1996-1997 (Box IO16)
    - Kraft-Kréma, 1992 (Box IO16)
    - La Poste-Diligo, 1994 (Box IO16)
    - L'Oreale (Kerastase), 1990 (Box IO17)
    - Marne et Champagne Diffusion (Covema), undated (Box IO17)
    - Milka, 1996 (Box IO17)
    - Minitel case study, 1989 (Box IO17)
    - Mobil, 1986-1997 (Box IO17)
    - Motta (Cogesal) Viennetta, 1995 (Box IO17)
    - Motta (Unilever) Magnum ice cream, 1995-1997 (Box IO17)
    - Natalie d'Oro (Margherita outlets) charity program, 1993 (Box IO17)
    - Nestlé Rowntree, 1992 (Box IO17)
    - Novell, 1996-1997 (Box IO17)
    - Oasis fruit juice, 1993 (Box IO17)
    - Orangina, 1996 (Box IO17)
    - Perrier, 1991 (Box IO17)
    - Philips, 1994-1996 (Box IO17)
    - Rank Xerox launch, 1992 (Box IO17)
    - Reebok, 1993 (Box IO17)
    - RoC Suncare, 1991-1994 (Box IO17)
    - Schweppes/Pepsi (Seven-Up), 1991-1993 (Box IO17)
    - Searle (Canderel), 1991 (Box IO17)
    - SFR Telecom, 1995 (Box IO17)
    - Silk Cut cigarettes, 1990 (Box IO17)
    - Unilever Brands Relationship Program (Box IO17)
    - Unilever mailers, 1997-2000 (Box IO17)
    - Unisabi (Sheba pet food), 1996 (Box IO17)
    - Warner Home Video (Box IO17)
    - General, 1992 (Box IO17)
    - Goldeneye promotion, 1992 (Box IO17)
    - WCJ France self-promotion, 1994 (Box IO17)
    - Woolmark, 1993-1995 (Box IO17)
  - Germany
    - Case studies for WI presentation, 1990 (Box IO18)
    - Eurotunnel Le Shuttle, 1995 (Box IO18)
    - Ford Ka, 1996 (Box IO18)
    - Hugo Boss, 1996 (Box IO18)
    - Schickes Auto Club gift catalog, undated (Box IO18)
    - WCJ Germany self-promotion, 1994 and undated (Box IO18)
  - Germany (Berlin)
    - Eternit, Rhombus mailer, 1997 (Box IO18)
  - Germany (Cologne)
    - DAF trucks, 1997 (Box IO18)
    - Ford (Box IO18)
    - Ka product guide, 1996 (Box IO18)
    - Mobil (fleet owner's magazine), 1997 (Box IO18)
    - Zeiss technical literature, undated (Box IO18)
  - Germany (Eschborn)
    - CNI, 1996 (Box IO18)
    - Novell IntranetWare, 1996 (Box IO18)
  - Germany (Frankfurt)
    - American Express (Box IO18)
    - Creative, 1993-1995 (Box IO18)
    - Reports, 1994-1995 (Box IO18)
    - Andersen Consulting, 1992-1996 (Box IO18)
    - AT&T Calling Card, 1993 (Box IO18)
    - Blaupunkt print advertisements, 1983 (Box IO18)
    - British Airways, 1993-1996, (2 folders) (Box IO19)
    - Colgate, 1990-1991 (Box IO19)
    - Commerzbank/Comdirect Bank, 1985-1995, (2 folders) (Box IO19)
    - DuPont Tyvek, 1994 (Box IO19)
    - Electrolux/Zanker, Lavita washing machine, 1990 (Box IO19)
    - Eternit, undated (Box IO19)
    - Ford (Box IO19)
    - Case study, 1994 (Box IO19)
    - Cougar creative, 1998 (Box IO19)
    - Creative, 1997-1998, (2 folders) (Box IO19)
    - Galaxy mailer, 1999 (Box IO20)
    - Kunden-Dialog program, 1991 (Box IO20)
    - Freudenberg, 1991 (Box IO20)
    - German Tourist Board, 1995 (Box IO20)
    - Henninger Kaiser Pilsner, 1990-1993 (Box IO20)
    - Hertz Rental Cars, 1989 (Box IO20)
    - Kodak (Box IO20)
    - Kodak For You, 1994 (Box IO20)
    - Olympics sponsorship, 1992 (Box IO20)
    - Kraft General Foods, Zo brands in Germany, 1990 (Box IO20)
    - Minolta, undated (Box IO20)
    - Mobil Oil, 1988 (Box IO20)
    - Novell, 1997, (4 folders) (Box IO20)
    - Pirelli, 1996 (Box IO20)
    - San Pellegrino, 1989-1995, (2 folders) (Box IO20)
    - World League of American Football, Frankfurt Galaxy, 1991 (Box IO20)
    - World Wildlife Fund, undated (Box IO20)
  - Greece (Athens)
    - Colgate, 1996 (Box IO21)
    - Ford Fleet Division, 1993 (Box IO21)
  - Guatemala (Guatemala City)
    - BySupport, Dr. Solomon's Anti-Virus Toolkit, 1997 (Box IO21)
    - Cake Gallery, undated (Box IO21)
    - Comcel (Communicaciones Celulares), 1994 (Box IO21)
    - Glidden/La Paleta, Club del Pintor, 1996 (Box IO21)